本作品之片源来自互联网，仅供学习、交流之用。请自觉于下载后24小时内删除。任何组织和个人不得用于任何商业用途，否则一切后果请自行承担！如果喜欢本片，请购买正版
-吃早饭了  -嗨  我是泰迪·邓肯
-Breakfast! -Hi, I'm Teddy Duncan,
现在是来自厨房的报道  老妈再次
Reporting live from the kitchen where, once again,
毁掉了一盘无辜的煎饼
Mom has taken an innocent pancake and destroyed it.
您是如何看待这件事的
Your thoughts?
你为何要通过叉子来羞辱我
Why are you insulting me into a fork?
我参加了南部高中新闻快报队
I'm joining the South high action news team.
-今天将进行首次会面  -噢  太棒了
-Today's the first meeting. -Oh, that is so exciting!
知道吗  泰迪  想当年我曾参加
You know, Teddy, when I was reporting for the...
西南丹佛社区大学电视新闻队
Southwest Denver community college tv news.
噢  有点儿意思  哈哈
Oh, how funny. Heh heh.
-想必我一定  -以前提到过
-Guess I must have... -Mentioned that before.
总之  当我播报时
Anyway, when I was reporting,
我总是有句很可爱的口头语
I had this really cute catchphrase.
就好像这句
It went a little something like this:
我是你们的新闻女主播  艾米·布兰肯胡珀
I'm Amy Blankenhooper, gettin' all up in your news.
早上好
Morning.
噢  有煎饼  好耶
Ooh, pancakes. Yay.
呃  还是在上班的路上买早点吧
Uh, maybe I'll pick up something on the way to work.
连老爸都不吃的时候  那就可以算是毒药了
When he won't eat it, that's a bad pancake.
我的靴子哪去了
Has anyone seen my boots?
看来查莉知道
Looks like Charlie has.
太可爱了
<i>That's adorable!</i>
邓肯小姐  请问你有意识到有时候老爸
Miss Duncan, are you aware that dad sometimes.
穿这双靴子出的臭汗  都可以倒出来了吗
Has to pour sweat out of those boots?
呦
Ew.
童言无忌啊
Out of the mouths of babes.
-这里是泰迪·邓肯  -还有艾米·邓肯
-This is Teddy Duncan... -And Amy Duncan...
-老妈这可是把叉子  -我是女主播
-Mom, it's a fork. -... Gettin' all up in your news.
■
本字幕由★迪幻字幕组★为您奉献
欢迎登录 www.Deefun.com
生活搞得一团糟
<i>Today's all burnt toast </i>
就要迟到  爸爸在叫
<i>Running late, and dad jokes</i>
我左脚的鞋子有没有人看到
<i>Has anybody seen my left shoe</i>
■
翻译： Johnny-Z
我闭上眼  咬口早餐
<i>I close my eyes, take a bite</i>
跳上车子  放声大笑
<i>Grab a ride, laugh out loud</i>
哎呀  老爸  鞋子就在房顶上
<i>There it is up on the roof</i>
■
校订： line
我也曾这样生活  我已经顺利走过
<i>I've been there, I've survived</i>
所以听取我的建议
<i>So just take my advice</i>
■
后期： Johnny-Z  sarina
宝贝  不要放弃
<i>Hang in there, baby</i>
世界有很多疯狂无奈
<i>Things are crazy</i>
可是我知道你会有美好将来
<i>But I know your future's bright</i>
宝贝  不要放弃
<i>Hang in there, baby</i>
不要怀疑
<i>There's no maybe</i>
一切终会如你所愿
<i>Everything turns out all right</i>
生活有悲有喜
<i>Your life is up and down</i>
但是请相信我  坚持就有好结果
<i>But trust me it comes back around</i>
你会喜欢将来的你
<i>You're gonna love</i> <i>who you turn out to be</i>
宝贝  不要放弃
<i>Hang in there, baby.</i>
查莉成长日记  第二季第十四集
Good Luck Charlie  S02E14  Baby's New Shoes
噢  嘿  老妹  要一起坐吗
Oh, hey, sis. You want to sit together?
好啊  乐意之至
Yeah sure, I'd love to.
-这个笑话永远不过时  -是啊
-Oh, it never gets old. -Yeah.
噢  等一下  那是达斯汀·里斯吗
Oh, wait. Is that Dustin Reese?
达斯汀·里斯是谁
<i>Who's dustin Reese?</i>
幼儿园时我们是一个班的
We went to kindergarten together.
当时他还有个马尾辫  直到
Back then he had a ponytail until...
你为什么剪掉了他的马尾辫
Why'd you cut off his ponytail?
那是我第一次用剪刀
It was my first day with scissors.
而且我还吃了个甜甜圈  我脑袋秀逗了
I had eaten a doughnut. I was out of my mind.
-你觉着他还记得你吗  -希望记不住
-So do you think he remembers you? -I hope not.
看啊  他来了
Well, here he comes.
你  你完全可以转过身啊
What... you could have just turned around.
呃
Eh.
大家好  欢迎来到南部高中
Okay, everyone, welcome to the South high.
新闻快报队  简称南高新快队
Action news team, or shant.
总之  我想为这次会议推迟而道歉
Anyway, I wanted to apologize for postponing the meeting.
正如你们所了解的  我从自行车上摔下来了  又一次
As you know, I fell off my bike... Again.
谁笑呢
Who laughed?
是我  我在笑别的事情呢
Me. I was thinking about something else.
-那你笑什么呢  -你第一次从自行车上摔下来
-And what was that? -The first time you fell off your bike.
言归正传
Moving on.
听着  你们中的某人
All right, one of you.
将会得到一个绝佳机遇
Is going to have a big opportunity.
新闻八台正需要一名青少年记者
The channel 8 news is looking for a teen reporter.
这个实习职位将有机会上电视
For an internship which includes a chance to appear on tv.
如果有兴趣
If you're interested,
请于周五前上交一份两分钟左右的报道到我的办公桌上
have a two-minute piece on my desk by Friday...
内容要丰富多彩  劲爆  热门  疼啊
Something juicy, explosive, hard-hitting... ow.
我会挑出一份最好的  然后上交到第八频道
I'll pick the best one and submit it to channel 8.
大家开工吧
<i>Now get to work.</i>
-噢  泰迪  是吧  -是的
-Oh, and Teddy, was it? -Yeah.
你是新来的  送你条忠告
You're new around here. A piece of advice...
不要爱上我
Don't fall in love with me.
放心吧
I shan't.
鲍伯  鲍伯  劲爆新闻
Bob, Bob, big news.
沃尔特·麦圭尔打电话来邀请咱们
Walt Mcguire called and invited us.
-去他的乡村俱乐部吃晚饭  -沃尔特·麦圭尔是谁
-Out to dinner at his country club. -Who is Walt Mcguire?
亲爱的  他就是医院里的头头啊
Honey, he's the hospital administrator.
我还总是谈到过他
I talk about him all the time.
我说怎么老能听到他呢
And I listen about him all the time.
噢  噢  哦  我跟你说
Ooh ooh ooh. You know what?
我要穿那身衣服  让大家还以为我是泰迪的姐姐呢
I'm going to wear that dress that makes people ask if I'm Teddy's sister.
得了吧  亲爱的  有人信
Come on, honey, has anybody ever...
我就很中意那套衣服
I love that dress.
知道吗
You know what?
我打算再买一双新鞋
I think I'm going to buy a new pair of shoes too.
而你也会想穿上那套西服的
And you might want to try on your suit.
我为啥想穿啊
Why would I want to do that?
自从返乡舞会后
You might have put on a little weight.
你可能长了点肉
Since our homecoming dance.
谢谢你用了“可能”这俩字
Thank you for saying "might have. "
-PJ  -达斯汀
-P.J.! -Dustin.
你来干什么
What are you doing here?
咱来一起上的幼儿园  记起来了吗
Do you remember me from kindergarten?
我  记不太清了
I... I don't know.
那是很久以前的事情了
It was... it was a long time ago.
你说的是哪年的幼儿园
And which year of kindergarten?
我给你看点东西
I want to show you something.
快出来
Come on out.
-搞什么飞机  -我是特意来给你理发的
-What's all this? -I came to give you a haircut.
噢  挺好  你心肠真好
Oh. Oh well, that's very nice of you,
但我经常去瑞秋理发店
But I always go to Rachel at crazy cuts.
-以后就不用了  -你啥意思
-Not anymore. -What do you mean?
啊
Ahh!
住手
No!
噢
Oh.
为什么我总是在这沙发上做噩梦
Why do I always have nightmares when I nap on this couch?
算了  再睡五分钟
Eh, five more minutes.
-你怎么和我坐一起了  -因为我没认出你
-Why are you sitting with me? -Because I didn't realize it was you.
你怎么这身打扮
Why are you dressed like that?
-我不想让达斯汀认出我  -噢  那个马尾辫孩子
-I don't want Dustin to recognize me. -Oh, the ponytail kid?
你怕他报复你
You're worried he's going to get back at you?
他已经出现在我的梦境中了  而且是在午休梦中
He has gotten into my dreams, my nap dreams.
以往午休梦境可是充满了橡皮糖和棒棒糖
That is a place filled with gumdrops and lollipops.
-他不该出现在那里的  -知道了
-He does not belong there! -Okay.
听着  对于你的噩梦我深表同情
Well, I'm sorry you had a bad nap,
但我现在遇到了个实实在在的困难
but I've got a real problem.
周五前我要上交一条有卖点的新闻
I have to come up with a good news story by Friday.
这可是我上地方电视台的绝佳机会
This could be my chance to be on local tv.
什么东西
Ugh!
你要想找有卖点的新闻  你就应该报道下
You want a good story, you should do a report.
这些神秘的肉到底是什么
On whatever this mystery meat is.
等一下  想法不错
Wait a minute. That's not bad.
我就来弄清这些神秘肉的神秘之处
I'll solve the mystery meat mystery.
这让人作呕的饭菜也许就是我打开胜利之门的钥匙
This disgusting slop could be my ticket to the big time.
-今天的午餐如何啊  -噢  太好了  谢谢
-How's lunch today? -Oh, really good, thanks.
嘿  亲爱的
<i>Hey, honey.</i>
-买鞋了吗  -买鞋了吗  买鞋了吗
-You get some shoes? -Did I get some shoes? Did I get some shoes?
我不知道  你来告诉我  闪瞎你的眼
I don't know. You tell me. Ba-bam.
哇  赞
Wow! Nice!
-的确  而且只需四百块  -什么
-Yeah, and only $400. -What?!
淡定  我会在晚餐后把它们还回去的
Relax, I'm going to return them the day after the dinner.
我只是租借
I'm just borrowing them.
就好像图书馆的书可以让你这个白痴看起来有点内涵
They're like a library book that makes my calves look hot.
亲爱的  没有哪家商店是受理穿过的鞋退货的
Honey, no store is going to take back shoes once you've worn them.
他们是不会发觉我穿过的
They're not going to know that I've worn them.
我在鞋底粘了层胶带  这样就不会被磨损
I'm putting tape on the soles so they don't scuff.
你在哪学的这招
Where did you learn this stuff?
这可是我上学那段艰苦岁月中的老把戏了
It's an old trick from my starving student days.
本以为结婚后就可以不用这招了
I thought I'd outgrow it when I was married,
但是养了这四个孩子  快看  闪亮动人
But four kids later and here we are... ba-bam!
我给搞糊涂了  感觉很不对劲啊
I don't know. Sounds wrong to me.
-你要是不爽四百块就你去付啊  -我去拿胶带
-Or we can just pay the $400. -I'll get the tape.
这么说来你在幼儿园里给个孩子剃了头
So you cut a kid's hair in kindergarten.
而现在你成天惶恐不安
And now you're all freaked out?
这是我做过的最蠢的事了
It was the worst thing I ever did.
不知道如何是好  也许我应该向他道歉
I don't know, maybe I should just apologize.
道歉  要是我就再给他剪一次  让他知道咱的厉害
Apologize? I'd cut his hair again, show him who's boss.
好了  同胞们  觉得怎么样
Okay, guys, what do we think, huh?
哈  为乡村俱乐部准备的
Huh? Ready for the country club?
不好说  老爸  扣上纽扣试试
I don't know, dad. Button the jacket.
有心无力啊
That's not going to happen.
那我猜你裤子上的文明扣
So I'm guessing the top button of your pants.
也遇到了同样的问题
Is out of the question too?
是的
Yes, sir, it is.
鲍伯  帮个忙  可以吗
<i>Bob, a little help,</i> <i>please?</i>
-快搭把手  -怎么了  怎么了
-Need a little help, please? -What? Whoa, what's wrong?
用胶带背面粘在你的鞋底
Turns out that putting tape on your shoes makes them.
你就可以去滑冰了
Just a little bit slippery.
是吗  那为何不换双鞋呢
Well, why don't you change shoes?
什么  难道让我削减魅力吗
What, and kill the glamour?
你觉着咱们交钱去乡村俱乐部
How'd you like to pay all that money.
去看看会有什么精彩好事发生这个主意怎么样
To join the country club and see that coming in?
神秘肉到底是什么肉呢
What is the meat in mystery meat?
为了找出答案
To find out,
我决定和莉迪亚  也就是我们的午餐阿姨
I decided to sit down with Lydia the lunch lady.
一起坐下  来问问一些尖锐的问题
And ask her some tough questions.
-还不错吧  -别急  嗷
-Pretty good so far, huh? -Shh! Ow.
好吧  莉迪亚  让我们直入主题
<i>So, Lydia,</i> <i>let's get right to it.</i>
和我聊聊这肉的问题
Tell me about the meat.
镜头有必要离我这么近吗
Does that camera have to be so close?
你为什么心虚流汗了
Why are you sweating?
因为你把一盏大灯照在了我的脸上
Because you're shining a very bright light in my face!
或者是因为你在撒谎
Or is it because you're lying?
到底是什么  莉迪亚  那肉到底是什么
What is it, Lydia? What is the meat?
-碎牛肉  -碎牛肉吗
-Ground beef. -Is it?
还是别的什么东西
Or is it something else?
神秘肉  难道就真的很神秘吗
Mystery meat... is it really such a mystery?
我是泰迪·邓肯  你我同行
This is Teddy Duncan and I'm on your side.
-意下如何  -我不能上交这份
-So, what do you think? -I can't submit this.
-为什么  -因为这里面没有事实根据  没有证据
-Why not? -Because there are no facts, no proof.
很抱歉  这的确烂到家了
I'm sorry, but it stinks.
但我需要这次实习机会  我想上电视
But I need that internship. I want to be on tv.
那你最好在明天之前在上交给我一份更好的
Then you'd better come up with something great by tomorrow.
-噢  瞧好吧  -有点不自量力啊
-Oh well, just watch me. -I don't think you can do it.
-说这话你可别后悔  -你有没有和我一样的欲望
-I'm going to make you eat those words. -Do you want to kiss me.
-想来次热吻  -没有
-As much as I want to kiss you? -No, I don't.
值得一问
Worth a shot.
-噢  电影太好看了  -太好看了
-Aw, that movie was awesome! -So awesome!
当血从那哥们的胳膊里喷出来时
When the blood shot out of that guy's arm,
-感觉太逼真了  -太逼真了
-It looked so real! -So real!
你们这俩小屁孩聊什么呢
What are you guys talking about?
-呃  没什么  -我们刚看了“斩首3”
-Uh, nothing. -We just saw "decapitation 3."
-没有  我们没看  -我们看了
-No, we didn't. -Yes, we did.
还记得他们用那个女人的头当保龄球时
Remember I almost barfed when they used.
我都快吐出来了
That lady's head as a bowling ball?
等等  等等  那电影的分级PG-13吗
Wait wait wait. That movie's rated pg-13.
（注：PG-13为不适于13岁以下儿童观看，13岁以下儿童尤其要有父母陪同观看）
谁带你们去看的
Who took you guys to go see it?
他妈  他爸
His mom. His dad.
我们多付了五块钱给那个售票员
We slipped the guy at the box office.
他就放我们进去了
Five extra bucks and he let us in.
你脑袋给吓傻了吗
What is wrong with you?
他就是那个人的卧底
She's a direct pipeline to the man.
而那个人就是我妈
And by the man I mean my mom.
好了  这么说来那个卑鄙的售票员
Okay, so that sleazeball at the movie theater.
接受小孩的贿赂
Is taking bribes from kids?
真是  太给力了
That's... Fantastic!
-给力吗  -绝对给力
-It is? -Yes yes.
这就是我要找的素材
This is exactly the kind of story I need.
这能把我送到我的国度  电视国度
This is going to put me on tv, where I belong.
你现在听起来就像老妈
You sound like mom.
闭嘴
Shut up.
呃  干得好
Ugh, nice job.
-我们现在大祸临头了  -抱歉
-We're probably going to get in trouble now. -I'm sorry.
嘿  想来点儿口袋里融化了的巧克力吗
Hey, you want some melted pocket chocolate?
真恶心
That's disgusting.
算了  来点儿吧
Yeah, okay.
-紧急情况  鲍伯  出现紧急情况了  -什么  怎么了
-Emergency! Bob, we have an emergency. -What? What is it?
-鞋没了  -大家不许动
-The shoes are gone. -Nobody move!
房子已经被封锁了
This house is on lockdown!
什么  你上次看见鞋是什么时候
What... wh-when was the last time you saw them?
呃  当我昨晚回到家
Um, uh, when I got home last night,
我把它们放进了盒子里  然后就去睡觉了
I put them in the box and went to bed.
再然后我起床想去卫生间  我就把鞋穿上
Then I got out of bed to go to the bathroom, put them back on,
去了卫生间  然后把鞋放回鞋盒里  又去睡觉了
Went to the bathroom, put them back in the box and went to bed.
等一下  你为什么要穿着鞋去卫生间
Wait, why would you put on shoes to go to the bathroom?
因为它让生活变得美妙
Because they make everything an event.
亲爱的  听着  现在唯一美妙之处就是我们要支付四百元
Honey, look, the only event right now is that we're out $400.
我们必须要找到鞋啊
We've got to find the shoes!
-嘿  爸妈  -嘿
-Hey, guys. -<i>Hey.</i>
嗨  为什么查莉身上这么脏
Hi. Why is Charlie so dirty?
我俩在院子里追着玩呢
We were playing Chase in the yard.
还因为她穿着高跟鞋呢  脚下一滑  摔倒了
And because she was wearing high heels, she slipped and fell.
-什么高跟鞋  -这双
-What heels? -These.
-不会吧  -哈哈  她穿上还挺可爱的
-No! -Yeah. Yeah, she looked pretty cute in them too.
我还用手机照了几张相
I got some great pics on my phone.
想看看吗
You guys want to see?
看
See?
挺开心的事  怎么哭了
It's funny, not sad.
嘿  达斯汀  你好啊
Hey, Dustin, how's it going?
我是PJ  不知道你还记得我吗
I'm P.J. I don't know if you remember me.
-我们幼儿园是同学  -是吗
-We went to kindergarten together. -We did?
是啊  是啊
Yeah yeah,
我就是那个被胶水把脸粘到桌子上的那个孩子
I was the kid who glued his face to the desk.
那个舌头被仓鼠轮卡住的孩子
I was the kid who got his tongue caught in the hamster wheel.
那个剪断你马尾辫的的孩子
I was the kid who cut off your ponytail.
噢  我想起来了
Oh yeah, I remember that.
是啊  就是我
Yeah yeah.
听着  我知道现在说这个有点儿迟
Listen, I know it's probably way too late for this,
但是  我真的很抱歉
But I just... I want to say I'm really sorry.
呃  别内疚了  都是很久以前的事情了
Eh, don't worry about it. It was a long time ago.
-你不生气吗  -不生气
-So you're not mad? -Not at all.
噢  太好了  我可以坐这里吃饭吗
Oh, that's so great, man. You mind if I stay?
-可以  可以  -太好了
-Sure sure. -Cool.
你不会又想剪我的头发吧
You're not going to cut my hair again, are you?
好了  好了  孩子们听着  计划是这样的
Okay okay, you guys, come on. So here's the plan:
盖比  你去买票  杰克  你戴上这帽子
Gabe, you'll buy the tickets. Jake, you'll wear this hat.
里面有个摄像机  可以记录下事情经过
It has a camera in it and it'll record the whole thing.
我戴帽子就不帅了
I don't look good in hats.
杰克  别这样  将就下吧
Jake, come on, we got to do this.
老兄  我这耳朵可是耍帅的资本
Dude, my hair is my best feature.
好吧  听着  如果你俩不能把这事解决了
Okay, well, if you guys don't go through with this,
我就告诉你们的妈妈们“斩首3”这件事
I'll tell both your moms about "decapitation 3"...
还有第一部和第二部
And "1" and "2."
-呃  这事也被你发现了  -现在发现了
-Uh, you know about those? -I do now.
至少我能反着戴吗
Can I at least wear it backwards?
这样更有嘻哈范儿
It's more hip hop that way.
虽然他属于智障系列  但他可以
What he lacks in brains he makes up for in...
用泳池来弥补
He's got a pool.
海绵
Sponge.
记号笔
Marker.
麻花
Pretzel.
-还能复原吗  -嘘
-Are they going to make it? -Shh.
在这关键的时刻
A very critical part of the operation.
我需要绝对的安静
I need absolute quiet.
-嘿  爸妈  怎么样了  -噢  苍天啊
-Hey, guys! How's it going? -Ooh! My gosh!
还有戏吗
Did we lose her?
-什么事  PJ  -这位是达斯汀
-What is it, P.J.? -This is Dustin.
他能在咱家过夜吗
Is it okay if he sleeps over?
-没问题  你好  -好的  谢了
-Sure. Hi. Fine. -Cool, thanks.
-他们在干什么  -我也不知道  可能在玩抢鞋游戏吧
-What are they doing? -I don't know. Playing catch with shoes.
去吧  去吧
Go go.
两张“斩首3”的票  谢谢
Two tickets for "decapitation 3," please.
噢  这电影的分级是PG-13的  小朋友们
Ooh, that's pg-13, guys.
而且我也没看见有成人可以带你们观看
And since I don't see any adults around here,
如果想买到票
If you want to buy a ticket,
可能需要一些手续费
There's going to be a handling fee.
嘿  不如我们看“小鱼的朋友们”吧
<i>Hey, maybe we should see</i> <i>"fishy friendz" instead.</i>
不不不  看着盖比
No no no no. Look at Gabe!
看着盖比啊  噢
Look at Gabe! Oh!
配音演员有
<i>It features</i> <i>the voice talents</i>
史蒂夫·卡瑞尔和罗西·培瑞兹
<i>Of Steve Carell</i> <i>and Rosie Perez.</i>
（注：史蒂夫·卡瑞尔是美国当红喜剧明星）
祝你观影快乐
Enjoy the show.
-好了  完事了吗  -没有  没完事
-Okay, are we done now? -No no, you didn't get it.
杰克一直在盯着“小鱼的朋友们”的海报
Jake was looking at the poster for "fishy friendz."
我也是情不自禁  那条鱼可是戴着眼镜呢
I couldn't help it. The fish was wearing glasses.
真是太搞了
That's hilarious!
好了  咱们再来一遍
All right, we're doing this again.
这次我戴帽子
This time I'm wearing the hat.
给你钱
Here.
杰克  你就老实的在这呆着
Jake, you wait here.
-一张“斩首3”的电影票  -你怎么还在这儿
-One ticket for "decapitation 3. " -Weren't you just here?
是啊  我在这  你在那
Yeah, I was here and you were there.
我付钱给你
And I gave you some money.
你到底还想不想再干一次这美差事
Now do you want to do it again or not?
好吧  你也知道这规矩
Okay, you know the drill.
手续费
Handling fee.
对不起  你刚才是不是向一个十一岁的孩子
Excuse me, did you just sell an 11-year-old boy.
卖了一张PG-13等级的电影票
A ticket to a pg-13 movie?
什么  我  我不知道你说什么呢
What? I... I don't know what you're talking about.
噢  是吗  你心知肚明
Oh yeah? Okay. Well, I think you do.
因为我已经用我的摄像帽录下了整个过程
Because I just caught the whole thing on my hat Cam.
想解释一下吗
Care to make a statement?
成了  不如  不如我给你
Yeah. How about... how about I give you.
两张免费的“小鱼的朋友们”电影票
Two free tickets to "fishy friendz"
睁只眼闭只眼  让这事过去
And we make this thing go away, huh?
快答应
Do it!
大功告成  我是泰迪·邓肯  少年记者
Busted! This is Teddy Duncan, teen reporter.
记住  当有新闻报道时  那就
Remember, when there's news to be reported, then...
那就是我报道的
The one reporting it will be me.
一会儿再修补这段
I'll fix that later.
-早上好  -嘿
-Good morning. -Hey.
为什么拿面镜子
Why are you holding the mirror?
因为咱俩现在扯平了
Because now we're even.
啊
Ahh!
Ah!
老兄  我刚才做了个奇怪的梦
Dude, I just had the weirdest dream.
是吗  梦到什么了
Really? What about?
听起来可能有点疯狂
It was actually kind of crazy.
为了报复我  你剃光了我半个脑袋
To get back at me you shaved half my head.
哇  哇  是够疯狂的
Wow. Wow, that is crazy.
-吃早饭吗  -好啊
-Should we get some breakfast? -Yeah, sounds good.
-你冷吗  -不冷啊
-Are you chilly? -No.
我有点儿凉  哼
I'm a little chilly. Huh.
我是你们的新闻女主播  泰迪·邓肯
<i>This is Teddy duncan</i> <i>getting all up in your news.</i>
觉得怎么样啊
So what do you think?
劲爆  有深度  有娱乐精神
It's hard-hitting, informative and entertaining.
这是我整个学期看到过的最好的  但我还是不能选它
It's the best piece I've seen all semester and... I'm killing it.
-什么  为什么  -那个售票员是我兄弟
-What? Why? -That box office guy is my brother.
-你兄弟  -是啊
-Your brother? -Yeah.
我长相帅气  他行为怪异
I got the looks, but he got the crazy.
等一下  我真的很想要这次实习机会
Wait, but I want that internship.
-他每天送我上学  -太不公平了
-He's my ride to school. -That's not fair.
-生活本不公平  -你不能这样对我
-Life isn't fair. -You can't do this.
-亲我  -亲你兄弟去吧
-Kiss me. -No, thank you.
好了  查莉  看来我的记者生涯
Well, Charlie, looks like my reporting career.
走的不太顺利
Has hit a little bump in the road.
噢  我的脚疼死了
Oh, my feet are killing me.
老妈  你为啥穿着高跟鞋去上班
Mom, why did you wear your heels to work?
噢  它让生活变得更美好
Oh, they make everything an event.
噢  商店不受理退货是吧
Oh. The store wouldn't take them back, huh?
当着我的面笑话我
Laughed in my face.
看  这就是很好的一课  查莉
See, this is a good lesson, Charlie.
如果你想搞什么诡计
If you try to pull a scam,
那你就等着自食其果吧
You're going to suffer the consequences.
给我  给我  给我摄像机
Here here, give me that camera.
不成  老妈  我正在录视频日记呢  别掺和
No, mom, I'll do the video diary, thank you.
不成  不成  不成  我有些话要对查莉说
No no no no. I've got something I'd like to say to Charlie.
离我的衣柜远点  好吗
Stay out of my closet, all right?
明白吗  下次你还想拿我的鞋子
Yeah? Next time you take a pair of my shoes...
你可以拿这双
You can take it from here.
好运了  查莉
Good luck, Charlie.
晚上好  欢迎来到“盖比与杰克看电影”节目
Good evening and welcome to "gabe and Jake at the movies."
我是盖比
I'm Gabe...
这些爆米花让我的手指看起来好有光泽啊
This popcorn makes my fingers shiny.
这位就是杰克
...And that's Jake.
今晚我们要回顾的第一部电影是“小鱼的朋友们”
The first movie we're reviewing tonight is "fishy friendz."
如今我发现这部影片情节俗套
Now I found it familiar and tired,
每个情节都似曾相识
Nothing I hadn't seen 100 times before.
-杰克  -太好看了
-Jake? -It was awesome!
每部电影你都这么说
That's what you say about every movie.
因为我喜欢每部电影
Because I like every movie.
那做这节目有什么意义
Then what's the point of doing this show?
免费的爆米花啊
Free popcorn.
-你个白痴  -你才是白痴
-You're an idiot. -You're the idiot.
-我不是  -就是
-Am not! -Are so!
这些就是本周的全部内容
That's all the time we have for this week.
欢迎下次收看  盖比看电影
See the next time on: Gabe at the movies.
嘿
Hey!